Guide to the Neal Lane papers, 1998-2001, MS 502 MS 502
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series II: Cabinet Files, 1998-2001; Files relating to the Office of Science and Technology Policy (OSTP) and the National Science Foundation. Memoranda, meeting materials, agendas, reports and notes relating to the various divisions of the OSTP: Environment, Science, Technology and National Secur
  - Sub-Series G: White House files, including articles, speeches and meeting materials for the President, Vice-President, Chief of Staff and others
    - President Clinton, OSTP reports, 1998 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - President Clinton, remarks and speeches, 1998 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - President Clinton, science and technology quotes, 1998-2000 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - President Clinton, meeting with Apollo astronauts, 1999 July (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - President Clinton, remarks, speeches, 1999-2000 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - American Association for the Advanecment of Science (AAAS), Clinton remarks on genetic discrimination, 2000 February 8 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - President Clinton, artcicles, memoranda, 2000 (Box 30, Folder 7-8)
    - President Clinton, speeches relating to science and technology, 2000 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - President Clinton, speech, California Insititute of Technology and related material, 2000 January 21 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - President Clinton, cyber-security meeting, 2000 February 14 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - President Clinton, presentation of medals of science and technology, 2000 March 14 (Box 30, Folder 12-13)
    - President's Millennium Vaccine Initiative, 2000 (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - President Truman's address before the AAAS, 1948 September 13; Clinton message on 50th anniversary of the NSB and NSF, 2000 December 12 (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - Al Gore, new articles, 1993, 1994, 1998 (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - Al Gore, articles, biographical material, 1994-2000 (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - Al Gore, articles, speeches, 1995-2000 (Box 30, Folder 18)
    - Neal Lane/Al Gore meeting, 1998 September 4 (Box 30, Folder 19)
    - Al Gore, memoranda, remarks, 1998-2001 (Box 30, Folder 20)
    - Neal Lane/Al Gore meeting, 1999 May 5 (Box 30, Folder 21)
    - VP meeting, budget discussions, FY 2000 (Box 30, Folder 22)
    - Al Gore, election campaign, 2000 (Box 30, Folder 23)
    - VP, cancer policy materials, 2000 (Box 30, Folder 24)
    - Al Gore, endorsements from scientists and engineers, 2000 (Box 30, Folder 25)
    - Al Gore, articles, remarks, election campaign, 2000 (Box 30, Folder 26)
    - John Podesta, memoranda, articles, notes, 1999 (Box 30, Folder 27)
    - John Podesta, speech, National Press Club, 1999 September 1 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - John Podesta, climate change principals meeting, 2000 October 23 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - John Podesta, memoranda, articles, 2000-2001 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - John Podesta, Progressive Policy Institute speech, briefing book, 1999 October 27 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Scientific Community Meeting, John Podesta, 2000 July 28 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Neal Lane/Hans Binnendijk meeting, 1999 November 30 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Gene Sperling, memoranda, agricultural and biotechnology rollout, 1999-2000 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Steve Richetti, notes, 2000 July 12 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Neal Lane/Sandy Berger, National Missle Defense, 2000 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Martin Baily meeting, "Summit on Innovation," 1999-2000 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series H: Reports, meeting materials, clippings and articles relating to a variety of science issues. Also includes reprints, articles written by Neal Lane
    - Research and Development (R, Research and Development (R&D), budget trends, 1953_1996 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Carnegie Commission on Science, Technology and Government, William G. Wells, others, 1988-1991 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - "Basic Research White Paper," 1997 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - United States Accounting Office, Bayn-Dole Act, 1998 May (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - S (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Events, presidential calendar, 1999 April - May (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - "Committed Partners for Action: A National Compact for Science Engineering in the 21st CEntury," draft, Judith S. Sunley, 1999 (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - "New Conpact," ideas, speeches, 1999 (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - Genetically modified food, GMOs, 1999 (Box 31, Folder 19)
    - Food safety meeting, Karen Tramontano, 2000 January 4 (Box 31, Folder 20)
    - Food safety meeting, 2000 March 1 (Box 31, Folder 21)
    - "Lard Almighty!" Pork-Barrel Politics...," The Sciences, article by Philip Smith on money for university research, 2000 Jan/Feb (Box 31, Folder 22)
    - NASA authorization meeting, 2000 June 22 (Box 31, Folder 23)
    - S (Box 31, Folder 25)
    - NSF, budget trends, 1982-1997 (Box 31, Folder 26)
    - NSF, 50th Anniversay Pubic Advisory Committee, 1998 October (Box 31, Folder 27)
    - OSTP, policy and information, William Wells, 1980-1997 (Box 31, Folder 28)
    - OSTP, information, articles, 1988-1994 (Box 31, Folder 29)
    - OSTP, orientation, William Wells, 1990, 1998 (Box 31, Folder 30)
    - OSTP, Clinton-Gore S (Box 31, Folder 31)
    - OSTP retreat, long range planning, 1998 July 17 (Box 31, Folder 32)
    - OSTP retreat, 1999 January 13 (Box 31, Folder 33)
    - OSTP, budget, "3 % solution," 1998 (Box 31, Folder 34)
    - OSTP, NSTC, 1998-1999 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - OSTP, building office space, 1998-2000 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - OSTP, organizational information, 1999 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - OSTP, articles, various topics, 1999-2001 (Box 32, Folder 4-5)
    - OSTP, long term planning, 2000 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - "Working with Congress: A Practical Guide for Scientists and Engineers," by William G. Wells, Jr., 1992 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - CSSP News, 1994-1996 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Congressional committees, 1997-1998 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Ehlers report, "Unlocking Our Future: Toward a New National Science Policy," 1998 September 24 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Industrial R (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Jeffersonian Research Dinner, 1999 November 15 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - David N. Schramm, memorial service, 1998 January 31 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Climate change report, 2000 (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Space station images, Atlantis mission, 2000 September 18 (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - Alexandria County Day School, visit to Washington, 2000 October 17 (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - "The Openness Imperative," Foreign Policy, by Neal Lane, 2001 (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - Articles, various science topics, 1990-1993 (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - Neal Lane, articles, clippings, reports, 1993-2001 (Box 32, Folder 19)
    - Neal Lane, biographical materials, [1993] (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - News clipping on Neal Lane, National Science Foundation appointment, 1993 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Neal Lane, articles, 1993 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Neal Lane, articles, 1994 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Neal Lane, articles, 1995 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Neal Lane, articles, quotes, 1995-1999 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Neal Lane, articles, 1996 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Neal Lane, articles, 1997 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Neal Lane, articles, 1998 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Neal Lane, articles, 2001-2002, undated (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Neal Lane, nanotechnology article, 2001 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - American Geophysical Union (AGU), water policy and research paper, 2001 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Essay in honor of Leon Lederman, 2001 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Neal Lane, letters to the editor, 1995-2000 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Series I: Calendars and daybooks, 1967-1992
    - Calendars and daybooks, 1967-1975 (Box 33)
    - Calendars and daybook, 1976-1992 (Box 34)
  - Sub-Series J: Rice University lecture notes and class materials, other research material, 1966-1993
    - Class record books, 1970, undated (Box 35)
    - Einstein talk, Fall Alumni Institute Lecture Series, 1987 November (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Einstein talk, Alumni course, 1989 November (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - General Physics, transparancies, 1986 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Baker College course, "Nuclear Age," 1983 Fall (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Baker College course, "Publish or Perish," 1987 January 19 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Lecture notes, Physics 570 1966 Fall (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Lecture notes, Physics 570b, 1966-1968 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Lecture notes, Physics 210, 1969 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Lecture notes, Physics 210, 1969-1970 (Box 35, Folder 9-11)
    - Lecture notes, Physics 572, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Physics 310a, 1971 (Box 35, Folder 13-14)
    - Lecture notes, Physics 520, 1971 (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - Lecture notes, Physics 310a, 1972 Fall (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - Lecture notes, Physics 310b, typed class notes, 1972 (Box 35, Folder 17)
    - Lecture notes, Physics 310b, typed class notes, 1972 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Lecture notes, Physics 141, 142, 1973-1978 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Lecture notes, Physics 572, "Atomic Collision Theory," 1972, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Lecture notes, Physics 574, 1975-1977 (Box 36, Folder 4-5)
    - Lecture notes, Physics 515, 1975, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Lecture notes, Physics 574, projects, 1975-1981 (Box 36, Folder 7-8)
    - Lecture notes, Physics 141a, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Lecture notes, Physics 141a, 1981 Fall (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - Lecture notes, Physics 141a, 1981-1982 (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - Lecture notes, 574, 1981-1984 (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - Lecture notes, Physics 142b, 1982 Spring (Box 36, Folder 13-14)
    - Lecture notes, Physics 141, 1982 Fall (Box 36, Folder 15-16)
    - Lecture notes, Physics 574, 1984 (Box 36, Folder 17)
    - OU research, 1960-1964 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Queen's University of Belfast, "Free-Free Transitions in Atoms and Molecules," 1964-1965 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Belfast, "Free-Free Absorption Coefficient," 1964-1965 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Belfast, "Modified Ert-Molecules," 1964-1965 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Belfast, "Molecular jt jm," 1964-1965 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Belfast, "Kerr Effect," 1964-1965 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Oxford research, 1971 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - University of Colorado, Colorado Springs, chancellorship, news clippings, 1984-1991 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous personal papers, photographs, 1989-1993 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series K: Subject Files: Department of Energy, OSTP, National Science Foundation, foreign travel files, "name files," relating to meetings and correspondence, and other
    - Department of Energy (DOE), Energy Resources R (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - DOE, portfolio project, 1998 (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - Rudman report, "Science at Its Best, Security at Its Worst, " 1999 June (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - DOE, Ernie Moniz meeting, 1999 October 20 (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - DOE, Secretary Richardson meeting, 1999 October 22 (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - DOE, stockpile stewardship program, 1999 November 23 (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - DOE labs, 1999 (Box 37, Folder 16-17)
    - DOE labs, Cox Commission report, 1999-2000 (Box 37, Folder 18)
    - Official of International Affairs, National Academy Press, "Protecting Nuclear Weapons Material in Russia," pre-publication copy, 1999 (Box 37, Folder 19)
    - Office of Science and Technology Policy (OSTP), Artie Bienstock, Jack Gibbons, M.R.C. Greenwood, meeting materials, memoranda, 1994-1997 (Box 37, Folder 20)
    - OSTP, White House discussions, 1998 Spring (Box 37, Folder 21)
    - OSTP, notes, correspondence, 1998-2000 (Box 37, Folder 22)
    - Joint U.S./Russian Plutonium Disposition Study, 1996 September (Box 37, Folder 23)
    - National Science and Technology Council (NSTC), federal laboratories, 1999 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - National Nuclear Security Administration briefing, 2000 January 25 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - National Science Foundation (NSF), correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 38, Folder 3-4)
    - Los Alamos, Summer School, articles, references, 1990 (Box 38, Folder 5-7)
    - University of Strathclyde, Glasgow, 1997-1998 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Carnegie Group (G-8 countries), meetings, 2000 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - Carnegie Group information, G-8 Summit issues, 2000 (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - Carnegie G-8 meeting, London, U.K., 1999 February 2-5 (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - Japan-Sweden trip, 1998 (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - U.K. - Northern Ireland trip, 2000 Summer (Box 38, Folder 13-14)
    - The Queen's University, Belfast, 1999-2000 (Box 38, Folder 15)
    - Australia visit, Robert Crompton, 2000 (Box 38, Folder 16)
    - India - U.S. Technology Forum, 2000 May-June (Box 38, Folder 17)
    - Dr. Murli Manohar Joshi, Minister for Science and Technology, Human Resource Development and Ocean Development, Government of India, 2000 June (Box 38, Folder 18)
    - Dr. Manju Sharma, Secretary for Biotechnology, Minstry of Science Technology, Government of India, 2000 July (Box 38, Folder 19)
    - Chun Lin, 70th Birthday Symposium, University of Oklahoma, 2000 October 11-15 (Box 38, Folder 20)
    - Illinois Institute of Technology, Chicago, 2000 May 12-13 (Box 38, Folder 21)
    - Publications, brochures, Hong Kong (Box 39)
    - China, 2001 November (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Japanese Delegation on Critical Infrastructure Protection, meeting materials, 2000 April 18 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Agenda, Aeronautics and space issues, 1998 September 11 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Biosafety protocol, 1998 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - National Bioethics Advisory Commission, 1998-2000 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - NSTC, draft report, "Federal Science Technology: An Agency Overview," 1999 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - NASA, future space launch meeting, 1999 June 8 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - National Research Council report, 1999 October (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - APS News, "Sinking the Test Ban Treaty," 1999 December 21 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Council on Competitiveness, annual meeting, 2000 April (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Neal Lane speech, AAAS Science and Technology Colloquium, 2000 April 11 (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - Human Genome issues, meeting materials, 2000 June 14 (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - National Science Board (NSB), Ad Hoc Committee on Strategic Science and Engineering Policy, meeting materials, 2000 August 4 (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - Restricted files (14-42)
    - Neal Lane dinner, 2000 (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - Draft, White Paper on Institute for Information Infrastructure Protection, 2000 (Box 39, Folder 15)
    - Name Files, includes meeting materials, clippings, articles on or relating to specific persons
    - Committee on Science, Engineering, and Public Policy (COSEPUP) and Government Performance and Results Act (GPRA), 1999 (Box 39, Folder 16)
    - President, National Academy of Sciences, articles, correspondence, 2000 February - July (Box 39, Folder 17)
    - InterAcademy Council (IAC), 2000 July-August (Box 39, Folder 18)
    - Bureau of Oceans, Environment and Science (OES) briefing, 2000 August (Box 39, Folder 19)
    - Space exploration topic discussions and meeting, 1999-2000 (Box 39, Folder 20)
    - French Proposal for the World Academy of Sciences, 1999-2000 (Box 39, Folder 21)
    - President, Univerity of California, 2000 October (Box 39, Folder 22)
    - "Seven Fundamentals of Effective Leadership," and Gregory E. Augustine obituary, 1998-1999 (Box 39, Folder 23)
    - PCAST meeting materials, 1999-2000 (Box 39, Folder 24)
    - Chairman, Council of Economic Advisors correspondence, 2000 September (Box 39, Folder 25)
    - Office of the President, correspondence, meeting materials, 1998-2000 (Box 39, Folder 26)
    - EMF pollution from devices and workstations, correspondence, notes, 1998-2000 (Box 39, Folder 27)
    - Blumenthal correspondence, notes, reports, 1990, 1997-2000 (Box 39, Folder 28)
    - Regulation for agricultural biotechnology meeting, 2000 May 3 (Box 39, Folder 29)
    - R D meeting, 2000 February 28 (Box 39, Folder 30)
    - OSTP correspondence, articles, 1999-2000 (Box 39, Folder 31)
    - Tribute, 1999 July - September (Box 39, Folder 32)
    - PCAST meeting materials, 2000 April - May (Box 39, Folder 33)
    - GUIRR correspondence, 2000 July (Box 39, Folder 34)
    - India meeting, 2000 May 16 (Box 39, Folder 35)
    - Human Genome Project briefing, 2000 March (Box 39, Folder 36)
    - India meeting materials, 1999-2000 (Box 39, Folder 37)
    - Correspondence, remarks to the New York Biotechnology Association, 1998-2000 (Box 39, Folder 38)
    - NSF Director, correspondence, clippings, 1999-2000 (Box 39, Folder 39)
    - American Meteorological Society, 1999 (Box 39, Folder 40)
    - VA/HUD/IA appropriations meeting, 2000 July 26 (Box 39, Folder 41)
    - Correspondence, Argentine Atomic Energy Commission, April 2000 (Box 39, Folder 42)
    - Steven Curvall, Rice Alliance for Technology and Entrepreneurship, 2000 March - April (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Betty Currie, notes, 2000 September 12 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Senator Tom Daschle, 2000 August (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - John Deutch, 2000 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Sidney Drell, DOE labs, 1999 September (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Jim Duderstadt, briefing materials, 2000 August (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Dolores Eher meeting, 2000 June 20 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Bob Eisenstein, reference, UCLA Vice Chancellor for Research, 2000 May (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Karl Erb, Polar programs, 1999 (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - George T. Frampton, Jr., correspondence, notes, 2000 August (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - Dan Freeman, correpondence, notes, 2000 June (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - Gerald Fischbach, 2000 March 20 (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - Leon Fuerth, U.S.-China Forum, 1999 January (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - Leon Fuerth, meeting material, 2000 (Box 40, Folder 14)
    - Jack Gibbons, meeting materials, 1999 October 15 (Box 40, Folder 15)
    - Jack Gibbons, correspondence, notes, articles, 1989-2000 (Box 40, Folder 16)
    - T.S. Glauthier, 1998-1999 (Box 40, Folder 17)
    - Dan Glickman, Science Advisor position, 1998 (Box 40, Folder 18)
    - mary Good, meeting materials, 2000 September 21 (Box 40, Folder 19)
    - Jane Goodall, meeting materials, 1999 May 12 (Box 40, Folder 20)
    - General John Gordon, 2000 September - October (Box 40, Folder 21)
    - Bart Gordon, 1999-2000 (Box 40, Folder 22)
    - M.R.C. Greenwood, 2000 April 6 (Box 40, Folder 23)
    - Senator Judd Gregg, 2000 September 21 (Box 40, Folder 24)
    - General Gene Habinger, 2000 September 20 (Box 40, Folder 25)
    - William A. Halter, 1999 (Box 40, Folder 26)
    - David Hamburg, 1999 (Box 40, Folder 27)
    - Mary Hanson, "media messages," interviews with Neal Lane, 1998-1999 (Box 40, Folder 28)
    - Jane Henney, FDA Commissioner, 1999 (Box 40, Folder 29)
    - Elgie Holstein, 1999 (Box 40, Folder 30)
    - Chris Jennings, correspondence regarding "gene therapy and informed consent," 2000 (Box 40, Folder 31)
    - Skip Johns, 1999 (Box 40, Folder 33)
    - Joel Johnson, 2000 (Box 40, Folder 34)
    - Bill Joy, 2000 (Box 40, Folder 35)
    - Tom Kalil, meeting materials, 1998 May 15 (Box 40, Folder 36)
    - Tom Kalil, National Economic Council, 1998-2000 (Box 40, Folder 37)
    - Jeffrey Kaplan, Director, Centers for Disease Control, 2000 October 18 (Box 40, Folder 38)
    - Eamon Kelly, National Science Board, 1999-2000 (Box 40, Folder 39)
    - Donald Kennedy, undated (Box 40, Folder 40)
    - Ruth L. Kirschstein, 2000 (Box 40, Folder 41)
    - Martha Krebs, DOE, 1999 (Box 40, Folder 42)
    - Cliff Lane, heavy metals expert, 2000 (Box 40, Folder 43)
    - Joshua Lederburg, 1999 May 17 (Box 40, Folder 44)
    - Ellen Lovell, 1999 (Box 40, Folder 45)
    - Frank E. Loy, State Department, 1999 (Box 40, Folder 46)
    - Frank E. Loy, meeting materials, 2000 (Box 40, Folder 47)
    - Shirley Malcom, 1999-2000 (Box 40, Folder 48)
    - Hans Mark, correspondence, articles, 1975-1999 (Box 40, Folder 49)
    - Sir Robert May, Chief Science Advisor and Head, Office of Science and Technology, U.K., 1997-2000 (Box 40, Folder 50)
    - Mike McCabe, 2000 November 17 (Box 40, Folder 51)
    - Richard A. Meserre, Nuclear Regulatory Commission, 1999-2000 (Box 40, Folder 52)
    - Ernie Moniz, 1999 July 21 (Box 40, Folder 53)
    - Ernie Moniz, DOE, 1999-2000 (Box 40, Folder 54)
    - Minyon Moore, 1999 (Box 40, Folder 55)
    - Jim Moorman, 2000 June 8 (Box 40, Folder 56)
    - Minister Hirofumi Nakasone, 2000 May 1 (Box 40, Folder 57)
    - Bob Nash, 1998 November 12 (Box 40, Folder 58)
    - William Albert Nitze, 1998-1999 (Box 40, Folder 59)
    - David Norcross, 1999 (Box 40, Folder 60)
    - Dr. Benjamin Payton, President, Tuskegee University, 2000 March 29 (Box 40, Folder 61)
    - Frank H. Pearl, 2000 (Box 40, Folder 62)
    - Secretary Whit Peters, 1999 (Box 40, Folder 63)
    - Anne C. Peterson, 2000 (Box 40, Folder 64)
    - Bruce Reed, Domestic Policy Council (DPC), 1998-1999 (Box 40, Folder 65)
    - Janet Reno, 2000 November 9 (Box 40, Folder 66)
    - Secretary Bill Richardson, 1999-2000 (Box 40, Folder 67)
    - Judy Rodin, Federal Research Misconduct Policy, 1999 September 1 (Box 40, Folder 68)
    - Lord David Sainsbury, 1999-2000 (Box 40, Folder 69)
    - Lord Sainsbury, 2000 June 21 (Box 40, Folder 70)
    - David Sandalow, OES, 2000-2001 (Box 40, Folder 71)
    - Dr. Barry Schneider, 2000 March 17 (Box 40, Folder 72)
    - Ivan Sellin, 2000 (Box 40, Folder 73)
    - F. James Sensenbrenner, House Science Committee, 1999-2000 (Box 40, Folder 74)
    - Harold Shapiro, NBAC, 1999-2000 (Box 40, Folder 75)
    - Cheryl Shavers, Under Secretary for Technology Administration, 1999-2000 (Box 40, Folder 76)
    - Phil Smith, 1999-2000 (Box 40, Folder 77)
    - Alexander Soifer, 1999-2000 (Box 40, Folder 78)
    - Douglas Sosnik, 1998-2000 (Box 40, Folder 79)
    - Gene Sperling, 2000 (Box 40, Folder 80)
    - Robin Staffin, National Ignition Facility briefing, 1999 September 10 (Box 40, Folder 81)
    - H. Guyford Stever, undated (Box 40, Folder 82)
    - Secretary Lawrence H. Summers, Robert Rubin, 1998-2000 (Box 40, Folder 83)
    - Strobe Talbot, Deputy Secretaty of State, 1999 December (Box 40, Folder 84)
    - Chang-Lin Tien, 1999 May (Box 40, Folder 85)
    - Harold Varmus,1999-2000 (Box 41, Folder 1-2)
    - Craig Venter, Celera Genomics Corporation, 1998-2000 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Charles Vest, 1998-2000 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Charles Vest, phone converstation, 1999 September 2 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Robert Walker, 1999 July 15 (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Wes Warren, 2000 March (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Congressman Curt Weldon, keynote address to the Monte Jade Science and Technology Association of Greater Philadelphia, 1998 April (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Ronny Wells, Jr., 1999 (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - Bill White, Amarillo National Resource Center for Plutonium (ANRCP), 1999 May 11 (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - John Yochelson, 2000 July (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - John Young, 1998 -2000 (Box 41, Folder 12-21)
    - National Science Foundation, subject files, arranged alphabetically by subject
    - Academic-Industrial Relationships, 1992-1993 (Box 41, Folder 22)
    - Amphibian decline, 1998 (Box 41, Folder 23)
    - Candidate Emergence in U.S. House Elections, 1997-1998 (Box 41, Folder 24-25)
    - Carnegie group meetings, 1998 (Box 41, Folder 26)
    - Climate change, "Global Change Resource Questions," 1997 (Box 41, Folder 27)
    - Congressional Q and A's, 1998 (Box 41, Folder 28)
    - Council of Scientific Society Presidents (CSSP), 1992-1998 (Box 41, Folder 29)
    - Council on Competitiveness, 1993-1995 (Box 41, Folder 30)
    - Department of Commerce, 1993-1995 (Box 41, Folder 31)
    - Department of Energy (DOE), labs, 1998 (Box 41, Folder 32)
    - DOE, 1990-1996 (Box 41, Folder 33)
    - Economic Productivity and Competitiveness, articles, clippings, 1989-1993 (Box 41, Folder 34)
    - "Educating for the Future," 1998 May (Box 41, Folder 35)